## DON DAVIES, B.TECH, PGDM

## **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

Motivated and proactive tech - savvy with excellent skills in analysis, assessment and technical documentation with industrial experience looking forward to take up a challenging job where I can use my technical and interpersonal skills as a part of a team to increase my knowledge in the field and strive hard to meet organizational goals.

## **EXPERIENCE**

### TECHNICAL SUPPORT SPECIALIST

Stax bill, Kanata, ON / March 2022 - December 2022

- Followed up with clients to ensure optimal customer satisfaction following support engagement and problem resolution.
- Provided accurate analysis, troubleshooting and testing of technical issues. Supported team's abilities and functions through positive customer relations.
- Utilized Postman for API testing and resolve customer issues.
- Created support documentation that empowered and enabled user community to extend skills, leverage system features and find resolutions to questions without intervention from support team.
- Tracked, monitored and documented interaction on tickets for timely resolution.

### TECHNICAL SUPPORT ENGINEER

Check Point Software Technologies, Kanata, ON / August 2021 - March 2022

- Documented client communication and resolution efforts via internal ticketing system.
- Utilized remote secure access technologies to diagnose and resolve customer issues.
- Participated in internal training and documentation on application features and functions. Managed Incidents and Problem tickets and support projects and initiatives.
- Utilized departmental tracking systems to track inventory and technical issues.
- Troubleshooted network connectivity and hardware issues.

- dondaviesc@gmail.com
- 1-647-383-6953
- ◆ 3000 Hungerford Gate, #3302 Kanata, ON, K2L 2T4

## **EDUCATION**

#### LAMBTON COLLEGE

**GPA: 3.48** 

## Mississauga, ON

Graduate Certificate Cyber Security and Computer Forensics (Aug 2019)

## Extracurricular Activities

- Actively coordinated Cyber Tech
   & Risk Cloud Security (RBC
   WaterPark Place, Toronto)
- Actively coordinated Cyber Tech
   & Risk AI (RBC WaterPark
   Place,Toronto)

## VJCET - MAHATMA GANDHI UNIVERSITY

**GPA: 3.2** 

## Ernakulam, Kerala

Bachelor of Engineering Computer Science & Technology (Aug 2017)

## CERTIFICATIONS

CCNA - Successfully Completed
Credential ID CSCO13504353

Linux Command Line (LinkedIn Learning certificate) - Completed

**Linux Shell Scripting -** In progress

**SQL** -In progress

### TECHNICAL SUPPORT SPECIALIST

Concentrix, Mississauga, ON / Nov 2019 - Aug 2021

- Procured, configured and tested computer hardware and software to fulfill requests.
- Listen attentively to customer needs and concerns; provide accurate information pertaining to order placements, delivery and shipping inquiries.
- Gathered and compiled information on operations and activities for reporting purposes.
- Participated in evaluation, testing and selection of security applications and systems.

### ASSISTANT MANAGER

Freshii (Restaurant), Mississauga, ON / Jan 2018 - Feb 2020

- Interacted with guests, resolved complaints and ensured exceptional guest service.
- Supported store to meet and exceed store financial goals.
- Created schedules to support engaging customer service environment.
- Supported store to consistently meet payroll expectations.
- Maintained close communication with customer during project life-cycle and beyond.
- Assisted GM in recruiting, developing, training and retained effective Team Members.
- Developed adequate scheduling to manage customer volume throughout hours of operation.

#### JUNIOR IT CONSULTANT INTERN

Tech Consulting Group, TCG, Brampton, ON / Jan 2019 - Apr 2019

- Configured hardware, devices and software to set up new work stations for employees.
- Experienced tracking defects using JIRA
- Designed, tested, installed and monitored new systems. Consulted via telephone to understand user problems, run through testing scripts and ask probing questions to locate root causes.
- Consistently responded to customer service emails within standard window for optimal response.
- Troubleshooted hardware, software and PC operating system issues.

# ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Intermediate in Java.

IOS and Mac-OS troubleshooting

Selenium- Test automation

Database: MySQL, Oracle

**SQL-Crud** operations

Knowledge of Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol (TCP/ IP)

Troubleshooting and Communication skills & Willingness to learn

Communication skills and excellent customer service knowledge

Documentation

MS-Excel, MS Office

Linux

MAven, Git & GitHub

Problem resolution

**Excellent Customer Service** 

Reliable And Consistent

Client Management

Software Support

Help Desk management

Active directory

## REFERNCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST